

# **Ana Alves**

## Multimedia Designer

I'm a multimedia designer living in Helsinki, highly motivated and multi-skilled with interest in UI/UX design...

I have 5+ years of experience in visual design, dealing and leading multidisciplinary teams in multiple environments due to projects and extracurricular activities.





Portfolio: anaflipa.github.io

E-mail: anaflipasa3@gmail.com



### **EDUCATION**

2009 - 2014

#### Graduation in Plastic Arts, FBAUP

Specialization in Multimedia

Coursework: Drawing, Web Design, Traditional Animation, Video, Photography

2015 - 2017

#### Master's Degree in Multimedia, FEUP

Specialization in Technologies

Coursework: UX/UI Design, Digital Games, 3D animation, Photography and Cinema

M.Sc. dissertation: "Transmedia Storytelling in B2B: the Case Study of StorySD". Final classification: 18/20.



#### **SKILLS**

UI/UX Design Transmedia Storytelling Illustration Photography Video Editing

Animation Digital Marketing

**Expert** Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD

Adobe Premiere

Bootstrap

Intermediate Adobe Indesign HTML / CSS

Adobe Illustrator

Beginner

Blender

Wordpress

Sketch



#### **EXPERIENCE**

2018 - Present

UX Designer at Polka Dot Studio

2017 - 2018

#### Multimedia Designer at Zappy Software

- Rebranding (Logo and illustrations for website)
- Social media management
- UX/UI Design for the future app
- 2015 2016

## Freelance Designer at worlDevelopers

- Logo and flyer design for clients

2013 - 2015

#### Creative at Porto de Magia

- Creation and management of multimedia/graphic content for the website and social media
- creation of a new sales point at Norteshopping



## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS & OTHERS**

#### **Projects**

Coop AR, 2017

StorySD, 2017

Future Places Citizen Lab: Behind the Curtain, 2016

MEDctrl, 2016

Downtown80, 2016

#### **Participations**

Invictvs Game Jam, 2017

Game Jam no Museu, 2017

#### Courses

Certificado de Aptidão Pedagógica (CCP) by IEFP, 2015 Social Media Marketing Strategy by EDIT, 2015 Cerveira Creative Camp by Canal 180, 2012